xarg.org 2019-05-28

# Privacy Policy • Open Source is Everything

This privacy policy governs how xarg.org stores, uses, and discloses information about its users. This policy applies to the site, along with related products and services Robert Eisele that link to this policy. This policy does not apply to websites, applications, or services that display or link to different privacy statements.

## Information You Provide to Us

When a user engages in certain actions on the site, they may provide us with certain kinds of information. This includes activities including but not limited to:

  * Subscribing to newsletters
  * Leaving comments
  * Providing feedback

The information provided may include details such as usernames, email addresses and IP addresses, necessary to operate the site safely. When you are asked to provide personal information, you may decline. But if you choose not to provide information that is necessary for certain products or features, those products or features may not be available or function correctly.

The personal information we collect depends on how you interact with us, the products you use, and the choices you make. We collect and process personal information about you with your consent and/or as necessary to provide the products you use, operate our business, meet our contractual and legal obligations, protect the security of our systems and our customers, or fulfill other legitimate interests.

## Information We Collect Automatically

 **Site Data**  
We may collect information automatically about users when they visit our site. This may include details about the user’s browser type and installed extensions, operating system, access times, language, IP address, and referring URLs, along with other similar data.

 **Web Browser Cookies**  
Our site uses cookies and similar technologies to provide features such as account logins, to remember user preferences, to engage in advertising and retargeting, as well as to analyze user behavior. Cookies are small text files placed on your device to store data that can be recalled by a web server in the same domain that placed the cookie. The text in a cookie often consists of a string of numbers and letters that uniquely identifies your device, but it can contain other information as well. We use web beacons (also called single-pixel gifs), for example, to deliver cookies and count visits.

## Third Party Sites and Services

Our site may link to the sites of our partners, advertisers, sponsors, licensors, and other third parties. We do not control the content of these sites, and are not responsible for their practices or policies. We recommend our users review the relevant third-party privacy policies to better understand how those sites and services affect their privacy.

Our site employs a variety of third-party services. These include content-distribution networks, advertisers, analytics, and monitoring tools. Some of these services store information about users, and may track individuals across sites, applications, and services. These services may collect information in a similar manner as described above, including, for example, IP address, access times, browser type, language, device type, and device identifiers.

By interacting with the site, certain information about user devices may be exposed to third parties using cookies and other tracking mechanism, these third parties include the entities in the charts below.

Service Name| Function| Privacy policy  
---|---|---  
Google Analytics| Analytics service| [privacy policy](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en)  
Google Fonts| Web fonts| [privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)  
Cloudflare | Content Delivery Network| [privacy policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/)  
Amazon | Affiliate Program| [privacy policy](https://affiliate-program.amazon.com/gp/associates/agreement/)  
  
## How We Protect Your Information

We adopt appropriate practices and security measures designed to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction of personal information.

Data exchange between the site and its users happens over a HTTPS secured connection and is encrypted and authorized by digital signatures.
